<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>niffdy</title>
 <link href="http://sjue.net/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://sjue.net/"/>
 <updated>2014-02-03T13:30:16-06:00</updated>
 <id>http://sjue.net</id>
 <author>
   <name>Brad Sjue</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>A Fragile Life</title>
   <link href="http://sjue.net/god/2014/02/03/A-Fragile-Life/"/>
   <updated>2014-02-03T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://sjue.net/god/2014/02/03/A-Fragile-Life</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.npr.org/2014/02/02/270637235/philip-seymour-hoffman-an-uncanny-actor-of-stage-and-screen&quot; title=&quot;Philip Seymour Hoffman Passes&quot;&gt;Philip Seymour Hoffman&lt;/a&gt; died the other day.  What a tragedy. It reminds me of just how fragile our lives can be.  That it only takes a small broken shoelace that starts us on the road to ruin.  Letting those little things add up in our lives can whittle away at you.  It begins to degrade your hopes, your desires, your belief that you are an awesome wonderful child of God that can accomplish anything.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know of a woman that after her father died began believing all of those bad thoughts.  She listened to that reptilian brain and began believing that she was nothing and that drugs were going to make it all better.  The voice she didn&amp;#39;t listen to was the voice of her husband who told her he loved her and that her two children needed her. That she didn&amp;#39;t have to do those things and that he was there for her.  She gave up and is now probably continuing down that path to ruin.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t let that happen to you.  FIGHT BACK.  If those voices in your head are telling you, you are not worth anything.  Don&amp;#39;t listen.  Call a friend, go to church, pray, go for a walk, exercise, do something - anything.  Once you begin to listen to all of the things that are wrong with you, that you are doing wrong, you start to believe.  DON&amp;#39;T.  &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What if I gave you more time in your day?</title>
   <link href="http://sjue.net/time/2014/01/13/Want-more-time/"/>
   <updated>2014-01-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://sjue.net/time/2014/01/13/Want-more-time</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;What if I stated I could give you at least one more hour in your day?  What would you do with it?  Would you start a hobby?  Would you read that book that has been on your shelf for three years?  Would you work out, spend more time with your children, learn a new language?  If most of us examine our daily habits, I believe that we actually do have time to do these, but we have to give up the mundane things that are consuming our time today.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe you could:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stop watching junk TV&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stop spending hours on Facebook or Twitter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stop any other online addiction&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stop &lt;font color=&#39;blue&#39;&gt;&lt;em&gt;insert your own time waster here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now try this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen to books while driving or on the train&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get up 15 minutes earlier&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take a shorter shower&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end if you want to have more time to do the things you desire, you are going to have to stop doing something else.  You decide what is the priority for your life.  &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
